♪♪
"Persnickety."
“挑剔的。”
Definition: fussy or particular.
定义：过分讲究或挑剔的。
- Correct.
- 正确。
Boom! Definition: nailed it!
砰！定义：完全正确！
Never mind persnickety.
没关系，挑剔的。
Let's get persnackety!
让我们来点挑剔的享受吧！
I've got some nice aged cheese, including a Danish blue.
我有一些不错的陈年奶酪，包括丹麦蓝纹奶酪。
Don't be afraid of the veins.
不要害怕那些纹路。
It's very approachable.
它非常容易接近。
[both] Eww.
[两人] 呃。
The only cheese I approach is nacho.
我只接近那种玉米片上的奶酪。
Don't feel bad, Nicky.
别难过，尼基。
It's nacho fault.
这不是你的错。
- Cheese me, bro.
来点奶酪，兄弟。
[gags]
[作呕]
This is so not approachable.
这真的一点也不好接近。
Ah, looks like the Harper house is the hot new hangout.
啊，看来哈珀家成了新晋的热门聚集地。
Is there anything better than a house full of happy children?
还有什么比满屋子快乐的孩子更美好的呢？
[Tom chuckles]
[汤姆轻笑]
[sighs] We should cherish this moment, Tom.
我们应该珍惜这一刻，汤姆。
[phone dings]
手机响了
[gasps]
倒抽一口气
Everybody out. Scoot.
大家都出去，快点。
Scoot. Leave. Andale.
快点，离开。走吧。
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走！
[overlapping chatter] - Let's go.
（重叠的交谈声）- 我们走吧。
- Bye. Thanks for coming. - Thank you for coming.
- 再见。谢谢光临。- 谢谢你们来。
- Don't leave. - See you later.
- 别走。- 再见。
Hey, no, you too. Beat it.
嘿，不，你也一样。快走。
- Scram. - What?
- 滚开。 - 什么？
I need the living room.
我需要客厅。
Mom, what the heck?
妈妈，搞什么鬼？
I was just accepted into the most exclusive book club
我刚刚被最排外的图书俱乐部
in Boulderly Hills.
在博尔德利山接受了。
What's a "book club?"
什么是“图书俱乐部”？
Oh, it's when a group of people read the same book,
哦，就是一群人读同一本书，
and then they get together and discuss it.
然后他们聚在一起讨论。
Why?
为什么？
Because they like to talk about books.
因为他们喜欢谈论书。
- Why? - Because they like it.
- 为什么？ - 因为他们喜欢。
- Why? - Because it's fun!
- 为什么？ - 因为这很有趣！
They are allowing me to host one event,
他们允许我主持一次活动，
and if all goes well, I can become a permanent member.
如果一切顺利，我就能成为永久会员。
So I have four days to read the book and get the house ready,
所以我有四天时间读完这本书并准备好房子，
which brings me back to my original point:
这让我回到了最初的问题：
get out!
出去！
So if we're not allowed in the living room,
所以如果我们不能进客厅，
where are we supposed to do all our livin'?
我们该在哪里生活呢？
Oh, I have the perfect place.
哦，我有个完美的地方。
You ready for this?
准备好了吗？
[mimicking trumpeting fanfare] ♪ Bup-bup-bup-bah ♪
[模仿喇叭声] ♪ Bup-bup-bup-bah ♪
[together] The garage?
[一起] 车库？
More like bup-bup-bup-bummer.
更像是Bup-bup-bup-bummer。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na, hey! ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
[whistling melody]
[吹口哨的旋律]
♪ ♪
[rhythmic clapping] - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Na na na na na-na ♪
♪ Na na na na na-na, hey! ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na na na na na-na ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪ - ♪ Na, na-na ♪
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
Remember when going home was something to look forward to?
还记得回家是一件值得期待的事情吗？
Now we're stuck in the garage, listening to the radio
现在我们被困在车库里，听着收音机，
and sitting on paint cans.
坐在油漆桶上。
At least your can had a lid.
至少你的罐子有个盖子。
I guess we could just hang out here.
我想我们可以在这里闲逛。
No, this is fine for after school,
不，放学后这样挺好，
but we can't stay here all the time.
但我们不能一直待在这里。
The store closes.
商店会关门。
And Dad starts charging us after our third smoothie.
而且爸爸在我们喝第三杯 smoothie 后就开始收费了。
[ear-piercing metallic screech]
（刺耳的金属摩擦声）
[all groaning] - What is that?
（所有人呻吟）- 那是什么？
[panting]
（喘气声）
Hey, kids, meet Terry the Bull.
嘿，孩子们，来见见 Terry 公牛。
[laughs]
[笑]
It's Terry Bull, get it?
这是Terry Bull，明白吗？
That's terrible.
太糟糕了。
Exactly.
没错。
Can we ride it?
我们可以骑它吗？
Oh, this is the kind of thing every kid would love to ride.
哦，这是每个孩子都梦想骑的东西。
But it's forbidden.
但这是被禁止的。
You putting that in the rodeo room?
你要把它放到牛仔房间吗？
Well, I was going to use this for my new office chair,
嗯，我本来打算用这个做我的新办公椅，
but that's a good idea.
但那是个好主意。
I could still sit on old springy for another day.
我还可以再坐一天旧弹簧椅。
Yah! Off to the rodeo room.
耶！去牛仔房。
[metallic screeching] [all groaning]
[金属摩擦声] [所有人呻吟]
Dad's Terry Bull is terrible.
爸爸的特里牛真是糟糕。
Ugh, great.
呃，太好了。
Speaking of terrible, look who just walked in.
说到糟糕，看看谁刚走进来。
[Nicky, Ricky, and Dicky] The But-er.
[尼基，瑞奇和迪基] 那个但-尔。
She's always one-upping us.
她总是比我们高一筹。
Yeah, remember last Easter when I brought chocolate bunnies
是啊，记得去年复活节我给班上每个人带了巧克力兔子吗？
for everyone in class?
她带了真兔子。
She brought real bunnies.
她带来了真兔子。
They were adorable.
它们非常可爱。
Hello, Harpers.
你好，哈珀家。
[together] Hello, Madison.
[一起] 你好，麦迪逊。
Oh, look. We're wearing the same jacket.
哦，看。我们穿了同款夹克。
[sighs] Here comes the "but."
[叹气] “但是”来了。
Buuuut mine's real leather.
但是我的夹克是真皮的。
Total But-er move.
典型的“但是”行为。
Ricky, I heard you got 100% on your vocab test.
里基，我听说你的词汇测试得了满分。
That's correct.
没错。
Much like all the answers on my vocab test.
就像我词汇测试上的所有答案一样。
That's great.
那太好了。
Buuuut I got 101%.
不过我得了101%。
I wrote a complete sentence using all the words,
我用所有单词写了一个完整的句子，
so Teacher gave me an extra point.
所以老师给了我额外的一分。
Teacher.
老师。
I could come over and tutor you,
我可以过来给你辅导，
buuuut I don't want to sit on paint cans in your lame garage.
不过我不想坐在你那无聊的车库里的油漆桶上。
Uh, our garage is not lame.
呃，我们的车库并不无聊。
There's tons of fun stuff to do in there, right, guys?
那里有很多有趣的事情可以做，对吧，伙计们？
Tons.
很多。
Yeah, tons.
对，很多。
Yeah, it's awesome.
对，棒极了。
Buuuut it's still a garage.
不过它还是个车库。
That's true,
没错，
buuuut it's a garage
不过它是个车库
with a chocolate fountain.
带巧克力喷泉的。
Yeah, and, uh, a vanilla fountain.
对，还有香草喷泉。
And a business center
还有商务中心
with a multi-device charging station.
配备多设备充电站。
I can't believe you don't know about the garage.
我真不敢相信你不知道那个车库。
It's totally the place to be.
那绝对是个好地方。
Good.
好。
Then I'll be there tomorrow.
那我明天去那儿。
Bring your tablet.
带上你的平板。
Uncharged.
电量不足的。
See you at noon.
中午见。
Oh, make it 11:30, before they break down the breakfast buffet.
哦，改成11点半吧，在他们撤掉早餐 buffet 之前。
Why did you promise her breakfast?
你为什么要答应她早餐？
Well, you promised her chargers.
呃，你不是答应了她充电器吗？
We have those.
我们有那些。
But a full breakfast buffet?
但一顿丰盛的早餐自助？
In 12 hours?
12小时后？
I'm just one man.
我只是一个普通人。
I'm sorry, but she's always but-ing us,
对不起，但她总是反驳我们，
and it felt so good to but the But-er.
能够反驳那个反驳者感觉真好。
So let's get our butts in gear and but her.
所以让我们行动起来，反驳她。
That's another thing.
这是另一件事。
Do you have any idea how much butter I'm gonna need?
你知道我需要多少黄油吗？
[Tom] Whoo!
[Tom] 哇！
[grunts]
[咕噜声]
Dad, were you riding the bull?
爸爸，你刚才在骑那头牛吗？
No. I told you I need a new office chair.
没有。我告诉过你需要一个新的办公椅。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[Anne muttering]
[安妮喃喃自语]
Okay, why am I bothering dusting? You're just gonna put everything in that box.
好吧，我为什么要费心除尘呢？你只是要把所有东西都放进那个盒子里。
I'm getting rid of clutter.
我在清理杂物。
These book club women do not mess around.
这些读书会的女士们可不是闹着玩的。
[sniffs]
[嗅]
Do you smell kids?
你闻到孩子的味道了吗？
Always.
总是。
Why do you wanna impress this book club so much?
你为什么这么想给这个读书俱乐部留下好印象？
Because no one ever invites me to join any clubs or committees
因为从来没有人邀请我加入任何俱乐部或委员会
because they always just assume I'm overwhelmed.
因为他们总是认为我会被压垮。
"Oh, look, there goes poor Anne.
“哦，看，可怜的安妮走了。
How does she get anything done with all those kids?"
她带着那些孩子怎么能完成任何事情？”
"She doesn't even look like she showered today."
“她今天甚至看起来都没洗澡。”
People say that?
人们真的这么说？
No.
不。
You know what?
你知道吗？
I may have four kids, but I always know exactly
我虽然有四个孩子，但我总是清楚
what they're up to.
他们在做什么。
Nothing gets past me.
没有什么能逃过我的眼睛。
Tell you what, why don't you go read? I'll take care of the living room.
告诉你，你为什么不去看书？我来收拾客厅。
[sighs] Really?
真的吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Oh, can you call Hank the Handyman?
哦，你能打电话给汉克修理工吗？
That light's broken.
那个灯坏了。
It just needs a new bulb.
只是需要换个新灯泡。
Can do that myself.
我自己能搞定。
[groans] Handyman.
[叹气] 找修理工。
Pfft. Easy peasy.
啐，小菜一碟。
Oh!
哦！
That can't be good.
那肯定不好。
Oh, oh! That's definitely not good.
哦，哦！那绝对不好。
[upbeat music]
[轻快的音乐]
Okay, just do it. Madison's gonna be here any--
好吧，就去做吧。麦迪逊随时会来——
Hey, girl.
嘿，女孩。
Sorry, I'm a little bit early.
对不起，我稍微早了一点。
Hope that's not a problem.
希望这不会是个问题。
buuuut I couldn't wait
但我实在是等不及了
to see that awesome garage of yours.
想看看你那超棒的车库。
Okay, I know we built it up to be super amazing,
好吧，我知道我们把它说得超级神奇，
buuuut...
但是……
it's even better than we said.
实际上比我们说的还要好。
[together] Welcome to the Quad Club!
（一起）欢迎来到Quad Club！
[dance music playing]
（舞蹈音乐播放中）
So what do you think?
那么你觉得怎么样？
It's nice,
挺不错的，
buuuut...
但是...
Buuuut...
[Quads] Buuuut?
[Quads] 但是？
♪ ♪
But nothing.
没什么但是。
This place is great.
这个地方很棒。
We did it. We shut her down.
我们做到了。我们让她停下来了。
I bet the But-er didn't think things would churn out that way.
我打赌那个说'但是'的人没想到事情会这样发展。
[all] ♪ And churn it, and churn it, and churn it ♪
[大家] ♪ 搅动它，搅动它，搅动它 ♪
♪ And churn it, and churn it, and churn it, and churn it ♪
♪ 搅动它，搅动它，搅动它，搅动它 ♪
Keep churning. - ♪ And churn it, and churn it ♪ - Look.
继续搅拌。 - ♪ 搅拌它，搅拌它 ♪ - 看。
It's Chet Acerman, the Ace Man.
是切特·阿瑟曼，王牌人。
He's aced every test he's ever taken.
他每场考试都得满分。
So he's the king of the nerds.
所以他是个书呆子之王。
Hardly.
不见得。
He's the president and leader
他是坚定研究儿童科学家组织的主席和领导者
of the Determined Organization of Researching Kid Scientists.
确定研究儿童科学家组织。
The D.O.R.K.S.
D.O.R.K.S.
Oh, so he's the king of the dorks.
哦，那他是呆子之王。
Yes, and he's coming this way.
是的，他正朝这边来。
Look smart.
表现得聪明点。
Hey, Nicky,
嘿，尼基，
this place is aces.
这个地方棒极了。
[gasps] He knows my name.
[倒吸一口气] 他知道我的名字。
He called you Nicky.
他叫你尼基。
He got the "icky" right.
他发音对了，是'尼基'。
Looking sharp, Mr. Harper.
看起来很精神，哈珀先生。
Hey, I know you. Aren't you in the third grade?
嘿，我认识你。你不是三年级的吗？
Grade is just a number.
年级只是个数字。
The number to be in here is fifth.
在这里，数字应该是五年级。
I totally understand.
我完全理解。
Sorry to bother you.
抱歉打扰了。
On my way out, want me to ask your assistant
我正要出去，需要我让您的助理
to grab you a drink?
帮您拿点喝的吗？
I don't have an assistant.
我没有助理。
What?
什么？
A big-time club owner like you doesn't have an assistant?
像您这样大名鼎鼎的俱乐部老板没有助理？
I know, right?
我知道，对吧？
I've been thinking that same thing ever since you said it.
自从你提到这个，我一直在想同样的问题。
Well, if you want one, I would love to apply for the position.
好吧，如果您需要一个助理，我很愿意申请这个职位。
- You're hired. - Dicky, could you run out back and grab me some-- - Bup, bup, bup.
- 你被录用了。 - Dicky，你能去后面帮我拿点-- - 等等，等等。
No one speaks to Mr. Harper unless they have an appointment.
没有预约的人不能和Harper先生说话。
Dicky.
Dicky。
Talk to my assistant.
跟我助理说。
Tell him I'm in a meeting.
告诉他我在开会。
Mr. Harper is in a meeting.
Harper先生在开会。
[upbeat music]
[轻快的音乐]
♪ ♪
Hey, guys.
嘿，伙计们。
Are those ribs? On bones?
那些是排骨吗？在骨头上？
Is that corn? On cobs?
那是玉米吗？在玉米棒上？
Apparently the lunch lady's grandson had a blast
显然，午餐女士的孙子昨天在四方俱乐部玩得很开心。
at the Quad Club yesterday.
她说只要他继续玩得开心，
She said as long as he keeps having fun,
我们所有的食物都会是可食用的，并且放在东西上。
all our food will be edible and on stuff.
那么我下午的安排是什么样的？
So what's my afternoon look like?
嗯，下午1点，重新涂抹发胶，
Uh, 1:00 p.m., reapply hair product,
1点05分，抖一抖，
1:05, shake it out,
1点15分，接受赞美。
and 1:15, accept compliments.
哦，天哪，我怎么记得住这一切？
Oh, man, how am I gonna remember all this?
这就是为什么我在你手指上系了这个。
[clicks tongue]
[咂舌]
That's why I tied this on your finger.
所以我才把这绑在你的手指上。
How did I remember anything before you got here?
你来之前我是怎么记住这些的？
You didn't.
你记不住。
- Chet just invited me to join his study group.
切特刚刚邀请我加入他的学习小组。
Today's the day I am finally a DORK.
今天我终于要成为一个书呆子了。
Hey, Ricky, see you at the Quad Club, DORK.
嘿，里基，在四方俱乐部见，书呆子。
Yes, chest bump!
没错，胸碰！
Handle this for me.
帮我处理一下这个。
Sure thing, D-man.
当然可以，D哥。
Uh, Mr. Harper wants to get a chest bump
呃，哈珀先生想和你来个胸碰胸的约定。
on the books with you.
记录在案。
How's 2:30?
30怎么样？
That works for me.
我可以。
- Good.
好的。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
[phone beeps]
[手机哔哔声]
How do you fix a hole in the wall?
怎么修补墙上的洞？
[phone] I found a handyman in your area.
[手机]我在你附近找到了一个修理工。
Would you like me to call Hank the Handyman?
[手机]你想让我给修理工汉克打电话吗？
[scoffs]
[嗤之以鼻]
[Anne] Tom?
汤姆？
[sighs]
[叹气]
Oh, there you are.
哦，你在这儿。
The book club meeting is tomorrow.
读书俱乐部的会议是明天。
And I have been shopping for seven hours,
我已经逛了七个小时的街，
and I couldn't decide on anything.
却什么都没决定下来。
Okay, I really need your help.
好吧，我真的需要你的帮助。
Now, which one of these pillows makes me look
现在，这些枕头中哪一个让我看起来
like I can do it all and I'm in control?
像是我能搞定一切并且掌控全局？
That one.
那个。
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
Wall yoga.
靠墙瑜伽。
Step away from the wall.
离开墙。
Why?
为什么？
- 'Cause I want to see what you're hiding. - Why?
- 因为我想看看你在隐藏什么。 - 为什么？
- Because there's no such thing as wall yoga. - Why?
- 因为根本就没有靠墙瑜伽这种事。 - 为什么？
Just get away from the wall!
只是离开墙！
[screaming]
[尖叫]
No, no, d-d-don't.
不，不，不要。
We had a minor electrical problem.
我们遇到了一个小小的电路问题。
- [gasps] - [stammering]
- [喘气声] - [结巴声]
The good news is, if I hadn't discovered
好消息是，如果不是我发现
the minor electrical problem, I wouldn't have discovered the...
这个小电路问题，我就不会发现那个...
major electrical problem.
大电路问题。
- [screams] - [stammers]
- [尖叫声] - [结巴声]
Tom, the book club meeting is tomorrow.
汤姆，读书会明天举行。
We need a handyman.
我们需要一个修理工。
I'm a handy man.
我是个能干的人。
Call Hank the Handyman.
打电话给汉克修理工。
I will be upstairs, crying into one of my pillows.
我会在楼上，把脸埋在一个枕头里哭。
I just can't decide which one.
我只是无法决定用哪一个。
[crying]
（哭泣声）
Show her who's handy.
让她看看谁才是能干的人。
Oh!
哦！
My hand! [grunts]
我的手！（咕哝声）
[upbeat music]
（欢快的音乐）
99...
100.
100。
Know what?
知道吗？
Let's make it an even 101.
让我们凑个整，101。
And so X=7.
所以X=7。
[applause]
[掌声]
Ricky, the only thing more enjoyable than that right answer
Ricky，没有什么比那个正确答案更令人愉快的了
is this garage.
除了这个车库。
Am I right, Science Bob?
我说得对吗，Science Bob？
You are, Aceman.
你说得对，Aceman。
When I founded the DORKS,
当我创立DORKS时，
I did it hoping to inspire young minds just like yours.
我是希望激励像你这样的年轻人。
Thank you, DORK-father.
谢谢你，DORK之父。
[phones ding]
[手机叮咚声]
Hmm.
嗯。
Oh, look, a text from the But-er.
哦，看，来自But-er的短信。
"I know you're all at the Quad Club,
“我知道你们都在Quad Club，
"buuuut my garage is having a grand opening,
“但是我的车库正在举行盛大开业，
and it's much cooler and way more fun."
而且那里更酷，更有趣。”
[snorts] Don't worry, no one's leaving the Quad Club for that.
（嗤之以鼻）别担心，没人会为了那个离开Quad Club的。
[phones ding]
[手机叮咚声]
Breakfast served all day?
全天供应早餐？
[cheering]
[欢呼声]
[Nicky] All day?
全天？
After six hours, you're just lying to yourself.
六小时后，你只是在自欺欺人。
It's lunch!
那是午餐！
I just got a text from the President.
我刚收到总统的短信。
I've got to go do science.
我得去做科学实验了。
You're going to Madison's, aren't you?
你要去麦迪逊那里，对吧？
Did you see what it says? "Breakfast served all day."
你看到上面写的了吗？“全天供应早餐。”
Whoo!
哇！
Mae, you're going too?
梅，你也要去吗？
Well, not if you don't want me to.
嗯，如果你不想我去的话，我就不去。
[sighs] No, it's okay.
[叹气] 不，没关系。
Good, because Mama needs more bacon.
太好了，因为妈妈需要更多培根。
I'll come back to tell you how bad it is.
我会回来告诉你它有多糟糕。
She'll never be back.
她永远不会回来了。
Why would you say that?
你为什么这么说？
When has bacon ever been bad?
培根什么时候变糟糕过？
[sighs] Mama's not coming back.
[叹气] 妈妈不会回来了。
[all sigh]
[大家都叹气]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
Look at Madison over there.
看看那边的麦迪逊。
That But-er stole all our buddies.
那个黄油脸偷走了我们所有的伙伴。
She's a buddy burglar.
她是个伙伴大盗。
I can't believe Chet kicked me out of the DORKS.
我真不敢相信切特把我踢出了书呆子俱乐部。
Talk about capricious.
真是任性啊。
Definition: given to sudden changes of mood or behavior.
定义：情绪或行为突然变化的人。
[crying] It was yesterday's DORK word of the day.
（哭泣）那是昨天的书呆子每日词汇。
This whole thing stinks.
这一切都糟透了。
Ugh. It's probably these fish sticks.
呃。可能是这些鱼条的味道。
Look at them over there.
看看他们在那边。
They're having surf and turf.
他们在吃海鲜大餐。
While we're just getting "urf,"
而我们只得到了‘urf’，
as in it fell on the "urf,"
就像它掉在了‘urf’上，
and they still "surfed" it to us.
他们还是‘冲浪’着送到了我们这儿。
Ah, Lucas.
啊，卢卡斯。
Sweet, you hooked me up with the steak and lobster.
太好了，你给我弄来了牛排和龙虾。
Bup-bup-bup-bup.
等等等等。
This is Madison's lunch. I work for her now.
这是麦迪逊的午餐。我现在为她工作。
Oh, but in the future, I'd still like to use you as a reference.
哦，但将来我还是希望你能做我的推荐人。
Okay, listen.
好的，听着。
We are not gonna let this little But-er get away with this.
我们不能让这个小家伙就这样逃脱。
We have to make the Quad Club so quadtastic,
我们必须让四人俱乐部变得超级棒，
there'll be no "buts" about it.
对此没有任何异议。
You're right, but how are we gonna top all-day breakfast?
你说得对，但我们怎么能在全天早餐之上再创新呢？
This is terrible.
这太糟糕了。
Terry Bull. That's a great idea.
特里·布尔。那是个好主意。
What is?
什么？
Your Terry Bull idea.
你说的特里·布尔主意。
I thought you said it was great.
我以为你说那是个好主意。
It is.
确实很棒。
Well, which is it? Great or terrible?
那么，到底是好主意还是坏主意？
Both.
两者都是。
Your great idea is Terry Bull.
你的好主意就是Terry Bull。
It can't be both.
不可能既是好的又是坏的。
Dicky, Terry Bull.
Dicky，Terry Bull。
Oh, I'm terrible?
哦，我是坏的？
I'll give you terrible.
我会给你坏的。
I fart on your pillow every night.
我每晚都在你的枕头上放屁。
I use your toothbrush to clean my retainer.
我用你的牙刷清洁我的保持器。
And you don't wet your bed, I do.
而你不会尿床，我会。
Oh.
哦。
Terry Bull.
特里·布尔。
Yeah, that's what I meant.
是的，我就是这个意思。
Love you guys.
我爱你们。
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ 哦，哦 ♪
- Hey, what do you think?
嘿，你觉得怎么样？
Oh, it's perfect.
哦，太完美了。
No, no. It's all wrong.
不，不。全错了。
I can't let this book club think that this is my first rodeo.
我不能让这个读书俱乐部以为这是我第一次参加。
- Anne, trust me. The house looks great.
安妮，相信我。房子看起来很棒。
Even the repairs look perfect.
就连修理的地方也看起来完美无缺。
Yeah, Hank did a great job.
是啊，汉克做得很好。
Yes. Hank did do a great job.
是的。汉克确实做得很好。
I'll pass along your compliments to Hank.
我会把你的赞美转达给汉克。
Perhaps you'd even like to th-hank Hank in person.
或许你甚至愿意亲自向汉克表示感谢。
Why do you keep saying Hank like that?
你为什么一直那样说汉克？
Eh, no reason.
呃，没什么原因。
[clears throat]
（清嗓子）
Oh, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
哦，不。不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
You didn't call Hank. You did the repairs.
你没有叫Hank。你自己修的。
Oh, 30 seconds ago you were loving Hank.
哦，30秒前你还爱着Hank。
Now you know Hank is me.
现在你知道Hank就是我了。
Do the math, Anne.
算算吧，Anne。
You love me.
你爱我。
[doorbell chimes] [both shout]
[门铃响] [两人大喊]
They're here. No, hands off.
他们来了。不，别碰。
All right, everything's set.
好了，一切都准备好了。
But how are we gonna get all the kids to leave Madison's
但我们怎么让所有孩子离开Madison的
and come here?
然后来这里？
Already got it covered.
已经安排好了。
I sent a text blast,
我群发了短信，
and any second now, this place is gonna get cray-zay.
马上这里就会热闹非凡。
Your house is much nicer on the inside
你家内部比从外面看要漂亮多了。
than it looks from the street.
嗯，谢谢？
Um, thanks?
我得承认，我对你能举办这次活动感到惊讶。
I have to admit, I was surprised you were able to host.
特别是考虑到你那些孩子们。
Especially with all those children of yours.
哦，你是说我的那些小天使吗？
Oh, what, my sweet little angels?
不，不，不。他们非常安静，行为得体，
No, no, no. They are so quiet and well behaved,
我有时候甚至忘了他们的存在。
I sometimes forget they're even here.
我有时甚至忘了他们在这儿。
[all] Bull, bull, bull, bull!
[所有人] 瞎扯，瞎扯，瞎扯，瞎扯！
[all cheer]
[所有人欢呼]
Yeah, come on.
是的，来吧。
They Quad Club is back, baby.
他们四人俱乐部回来了，宝贝。
And so is Mama.
还有妈妈也回来了。
[kids] Bull! Bull! Bull! Bull!
[孩子们] 瞎扯！瞎扯！瞎扯！瞎扯！
[loudly] So Sunsets of Tuscany.
[大声地] 所以《托斯卡纳的日落》。
I found it interesting how the sunsets were--
我发现日落的方式很有趣——
Are those your quiet and well behaved children
那些是你所说的安静又守规矩的孩子吗？
making all that noise?
制造那么多噪音？
What noise?
什么噪音？
Scone?
司康饼？
[Tom chuckles] Oh, no, she didn't.
[汤姆轻笑] 哦，不，她没有。
Oh, hello, ladies.
哦，女士们，你们好。
Sorry to interrupt.
抱歉打扰了。
Oh, it's a little dark-- dark in here.
哦，这里有点暗——暗。
[clears throat]
[清嗓子]
Perhaps while Anne enlightens your intellect,
或许在安启迪你们智慧的同时，
I can enlighten the room.
我可以照亮这个房间。
[kids cheering]
孩子们欢呼
[sparks]
火花四溅
[all] Bull! Bull! Bull! Bull! Bull!
所有人齐声喊：Bull! Bull! Bull! Bull! Bull!
[sparks]
火花四溅
[mechanical bull bellows]
机械公牛咆哮
Whoa, he got terrible in a hurry.
哇，他突然变得很糟糕。
This is probably why it's forbidden.
这可能就是为什么它被禁止的原因。
[bull bellowing]
公牛咆哮
He's getting away.
他要逃走了。
I got this.
我能搞定这个。
[bull bellows]
[牛吼叫]
[gasps] I got him.
[喘气] 我抓到他了。
[all] Oh, whoa!
[所有人] 哦，哇！
[bull bellowing]
[牛吼叫]
[yelling] Tea, anyone?
[喊叫] 有人要茶吗？
What is going on out there?
外面发生了什么？
It sounds like a stampede.
听起来像是一群牛在奔跑。
It's not a stampede.
这不是一群牛在奔跑。
What do you think, I live in a barn?
你以为我住在牛棚里吗？
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
[bull bellowing]
[公牛吼叫]
[ladies shrieking]
[女士们尖叫]
Oh, was your book club meeting today?
哦，你们今天的读书会吗？
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
Did they hurt you?
她们伤到你了吗？
This is terrible.
这太糟糕了。
Oh, I'm sorry, where are my manners?
哦，对不起，我真是失礼了。
[chuckles] Yes, and, Terry Bull,
[轻笑] 是的，还有，泰瑞·布尔，
these are the book club ladies.
这些是读书会的女士们。
I think we've seen enough.
我想我们已经看够了。
Oh, no, no, no, no, please.
哦，不，不，不，不，请别这样。
I can explain.
我可以解释。
I have never seen these people before in my life.
我这辈子从未见过这些人。
Ladies, let's go.
女士们，我们走吧。
No, no, no, no, no. Please, please don't go.
不，不，不，不，不。请，请别走。
[stammering] I have lady fingers.
我...我有女士的手指。
And man feet.
还有男人的脚。
[softly] Not the time, Dad.
现在不是时候，爸爸。
Hello, Harpers.
你好，哈珀一家。
I heard your party was a smash.
我听说你们的派对很成功。
Buuuut...
但是...
You know what, Madison, save your "buts."
你知道吗，麦迪逊，省省你的'但是'吧。
If you have to have the better garage, the better jacket,
如果你需要更好的车库，更好的夹克，
or the better test score to feel like a better person, that's fine by us.
或者更好的考试成绩来感觉自己是个更好的人，我们没意见。
Yeah, because if there's one thing
是啊，因为如果有一件事
our mother's massive book club disaster has taught us,
我们妈妈那次大规模的读书会灾难教会了我们，
it's that if you care too much about what other people think,
那就是如果你太在乎别人怎么想，
you'll do stuff that'll get you in trouble.
你会做一些会给自己惹麻烦的事。
Unless we're not in trouble.
除非我们没惹麻烦。
Oh, we're in trouble.
哦，我们有麻烦了。
Well, I'm sure there's a lesson in there somewhere
嗯，我确信那里某个地方也有一个教训
for me as well,
对我来说也是，
buuuut I don't care.
但是我不在乎。
[sighs] I'm sorry, kids.
[叹气] 对不起，孩子们。
I guess I kind of set a bad example.
我想我有点树立了一个坏榜样。
But I think we all learned something here today.
但我认为我们今天在这里都学到了一些东西。
Yup. No good comes from reading.
是的。读书没有好处。
[sparks] [bull bellows]
[火花] [公牛吼叫]
[Tom] Oh, ah!
[汤姆] 哦，啊！
How do you stop a mechanical bull from charging?
你怎么阻止一匹机械公牛冲锋？
[phone] Take away his credit card. [laughs]
拿走他的信用卡。
[bull bellows]
[Tom] Go, go, go, go, go, go!
快，快，快，快，快，快！
[bull bellows]
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
[whistling]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪